http://www.safety-usa.com/legal.htm

Last Updated: March 2020
DriverSafety USA (or “we”) recognize(s) that your privacy and the protection of your personal information are important to you (“User”, “you” or “your”) when enrolling in our programs. This statement discloses how DRIVERSAFETY USA helps protect your personal information while using the DRIVERSAFETY USA website (“www.SAFETY-USA.com” or “Web Site”). It does not apply to other online or offline websites, products or services, whether linked or otherwise associated with www.SAFETY-USA.com.DRIVERSAFETY USA seeks to provide, through our DriverSafety USA courses, high quality driving education and safety programs and other related services (“DRIVERSAFETY USA Products and Services”) through electronic formats, including the Internet, accessed principally through www.SAFETY-USA.com. By using the Web Site and DRIVERSAFETY USA Products and Services, you consent to the data use and practices described in this statement.DRIVERSAFETY USA'S COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONWhy We Collect Personal InformationAs described in greater detail below, DRIVERSAFETY USA collects and processes personal and financial information for several reasons: (1) to provide for your user identification and authentication, (2) to facilitate registration and payment for DRIVERSAFETY USA Products and Services, (3) to meet certain State or Court requirements pertaining to your identification and validation during courses, (4) to facilitate the delivery of course Certificates of Completion and other documents, as applicable, to you and (5) to improve security and provide customer support for you.What Information is CollectedWhen you register for DRIVERSAFETY USA Products and Services, you will be asked to provide certain personal information that will be stored in a secure and confidential "profile" (“User Profile”.) The amount of information we request from you will vary depending on the specific course purchased, but the User Profile may contain information about you, including the following: your (1) e-mail address, (2) legal name, (3) driver’s license number and state where issued, (4) license plate number for your vehicle, (5) social security number, (6) home address, including street address, city, state or territory and ZIP code or postal code, (7) telephone number, (8) primary language, (9) date of birth and (10) gender.When you register for a DRIVERSAFETY USA course, you will be assigned a username and asked to create a password for your account. You will also be requested to provide a secret question and answer. You will use your secret question and answer to help verify your identity to DRIVERSAFETY USA representatives when there are account issues, such as a request to reset your password.DRIVERSAFETY USA’S USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONHow DRIVERSAFETY USA Will NOT Use Your Personal Information:DRIVERSAFETY USA will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.DRIVERSAFETY USA will not use or share your personal information in a manner that differs from what is described in this Privacy Statement without your prior consent.How DRIVERSAFETY USA Uses Your Personal InformationDRIVERSAFETY USA uses your personal information for the operation and maintenance of your Web Site account and to provide DRIVERSAFETY USA Products and Services, as described above. As an example, DRIVERSAFETY USA uses your e-mail address, if provided, to send you a welcome e-mail message when you first register, confirming your enrollment in the DRIVERSAFETY USA course for which you register and telling you how to manage your Web Site account. DRIVERSAFETY USA may also send you e-mail messages about DRIVERSAFETY USA Products and Services and any benefits you have accrued as a User. DRIVERSAFETY USA’S GENERAL DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONDRIVERSAFETY USA may hire other companies to provide certain services on our behalf, such as providing customer support or performing statistical or other analyses of our products, services, Web Site or other areas of our business. DRIVERSAFETY USA will provide these companies with only those items of your personal information needed to deliver the services, and the companies and their employees are prohibited from using that personal information for any other purpose.DRIVERSAFETY USA may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process served on DRIVERSAFETY USA; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DRIVERSAFETY USA or its affiliates; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Web Site, or the public.DRIVERSAFETY USA'S DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION TO OTHER SITES AND SERVICESThe information stored by DRIVERSAFETY USA is not shared with other company sites or services, other than as described above.The information is, however, shared with governmental agencies in order to provide DRIVERSAFETY USA courses to users and to remain in compliance with State and other regulatory requirements, as applicable. www.SAFETY-USA.com is registered with independent, industry-recognized, certification and privacy assurance organizations, including Authorize.net and BBBOnLine.Nevertheless, we do not control or monitor the privacy practices of sites linked to the Web Site, and the privacy practices of those sites will vary. You should carefully review the privacy statement for each of those sites you visit in order to determine how each of those sites or services may use any information it collects.If DRIVERSAFETY USA becomes aware of ongoing, site-specific privacy issues with a linked site or service, we will work to address those issues with the site or service. If at any time you believe that a linked site has not adhered to these principles, please notify us at privacy@SAFETY-USA.com.MANAGING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONAccess to Your Personal InformationDuring the course, you can add, correct or update your password, address, e-mail address or phone number.Security and Storage of Your Personal InformationDRIVERSAFETY USA is committed to protecting the security of all your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access and that are in controlled facilities. Any time DRIVERSAFETY USA transmits your information, we use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. This protects the confidentiality and security of your personal and payment information while it is transmitted over the Internet.You must type the correct username and password to access certain Web Site information, including DRIVERSAFETY USA courses in which you enroll. It is your responsibility to ensure the security of your Web Site account password and not to reveal this information to others. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. We recommend that you change your password periodically, using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure that you use a secure browser.DRIVERSAFETY USA stores and processes any personal information it collects from you in the United States and not in any other country.Use of “Cookies”A cookie is a very small text file that a Web site saves to your computer's hard disk to store information that you provide about yourself or to store your preferences.DRIVERSAFETY USA uses cookies whenever you sign in. These allow you to move from page to page within restricted areas of the site without having to log in again, and to remember any preferences you choose, such as language selection.CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENTDRIVERSAFETY USA may update this Privacy Statement at any time. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top and bottom of the Privacy Statement.
DRIVERSAFETY USA will include a link in this Privacy Statement for you to use to “opt out” for any updates to this Privacy Statement that expand the sharing or use of your personal and payment information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Statement during your Enrollment.CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you have questions regarding this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail message to: privacy@SAFETY-USA.com. You can also contact DRIVERSAFETY USA at:DriverSafety USA2633 Malboona Mews Dr.New Braunfels, TX
78132Legal Notices and Terms of UseLast Updated: March 2020DRIVERSAFETY USA or “the Company” offers access to http://www.SAFETY-USA.com/ (the “Web Site”) and enrollment in the DriverSafety USA courses offered by DRIVERSAFETY USA (the “Courses”) under the terms and conditions described herein, in addition to any other terms and conditions that may also apply. By enrolling in one or more of the Courses, you (the “User”, “you” or “your”) are agreeing to these terms and conditions. DRIVERSAFETY USA reserves the right to change these terms and conditions from time to time, at its sole discretion and without prior notice, with the sole exception of the terms and conditions pertaining to information privacy which require notice, as disclosed in the DRIVERSAFETY USA Privacy Policy.The Courses contain information from other publications, government agencies and other third-party sources (the “Third-party Information”). This Third-party Information is included in the Courses for informational purposes only. The inclusion of such information does not represent endorsements by DRIVERSAFETY USA of the information or any products or services referred to therein or otherwise. Such Third-party Information is subject to change, and DRIVERSAFETY USA is not responsible for its accuracy.DRIVERSAFETY USA does not guarantee the sequence, accuracy or completeness of any information or data presented in the Courses, nor shall DRIVERSAFETY USA be liable in any way to the User or to any other person for any delays, inaccuracies, errors in, or omission of information or data or for any actions taken in reliance thereon, or for any damages arising therefrom or occasioned thereby or by reason of nonperformance, or interruption, or termination of the information or data for any cause whatsoever.COPYRIGHT INFORMATIONThe Web Site and the information contained within the Web Site, including the Courses themselves, are protected by applicable laws, including copyright laws. The Web Site may not be used except as provided herein and as otherwise stated on the Web Site.PUBLICATIONUnless expressly permitted in writing by DRIVERSAFETY USA, you are permitted to view, but not to copy, print, and distribute documents and text contained within Web Site, the Courses or related documentation. Any documents and text that you are expressly permitted in writing to copy, print, and distribute from the Web Site, the Courses or related documentation are subject, in any event, to your agreement that:1. Your use of such documents and text is for informational, personal, and noncommercial purposes only;2. You will not modify the documents or graphics;3. You will not copy or distribute graphics separate from their accompanying text; and you will not quote materials out of their context;4. You will display the copyright notice set forth above, on all documents or portions of documents, and retain all other copyright notices and other proprietary notices on every copy made by you.You agree in advance that DRIVERSAFETY USA may revoke any express permission granted at any time, and if it does so, upon notification or request you will immediately cease and desist all activities previously conducted pursuant to this permission. This permission does not, under any circumstances, include permission to copy the content, design elements, look, feel, or layout included in the Web Site, the Courses or related documentation for your own business purposes. Those elements of the Web Site are protected by law, such as trade dress, trademark, copyright, unfair competition, and other laws, and may not be copied or imitated in any manner.Except as specifically stated herein, nothing contained on the Web Site should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel or otherwise, any license or right to use any trademark, logo or service mark of DRIVERSAFETY USA or any other party that may be displayed on the Web Site without the written permission of DRIVERSAFETY USA or such third party that may own such mark or logo. Your use of such marks or logos, or any other content on the Web Site, is strictly prohibited, except as stated herein. You are also advised that DRIVERSAFETY USA will fully aggressively enforce its intellectual property rights
of the law, including the seeking of criminal prosecution.DISCLAIMERSUNLESS EXPRESSLY OTHERWISE PROVIDED IN A WRITTEN AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND DRIVERSAFETY USA, NEITHER DRIVERSAFETY USA NOR ANY THIRD PARTY HAS CONFERRED UPON YOU BY IMPLICATION, ESTOPPEL, OR OTHERWISE, ANY LICENSE OR RIGHTS UNDER ANY PATENT, TRADEMARK OR COPYRIGHT.EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY OTHERWISE PROVIDED IN A WRITTEN AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND DRIVERSAFETY USA, THE COURSES, AND ALL RELATED DOCUMENTATION, ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER, AND DRIVERSAFETY USA HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. FURTHER, DRIVERSAFETY USA DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES OF NON-INFRINGEMENT, TITLE OR QUIET ENJOYMENT. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL DRIVERSAFETY USA BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM THE LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS, IN ANY ACTION FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT OR WARRANTY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE COURSES OR RELATED DOCUMENTATION. SOME JURISDICTIONS MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO SOME OF THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. DRIVERSAFETY USA ALSO ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY, AND SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR, ANY DAMAGES TO, OR VIRUSES THAT MAY INFECT, YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT OR OTHER PROPERTY ON ACCOUNT OF YOUR ACCESS TO, USE OF, OR BROWSING IN THE WEB SITE OR YOUR DOWNLOADING OF ANY MATERIALS, DATA, TEXT, IMAGES, VIDEO OR AUDIO FROM THE WEB SITE OR BY OR FROM TAKING OR OTHERWISE USING ANY COURSE OFFERED ON THE WEB SITE.YOU ASSUME ALL RISKS RELATING TO AND/OR ARISING FROM THE SUITABILITY AND ACCURACY OF THE COURSES AND RELATED DOCUMENTATION. THE COURSES AND RELATED DOCUMENTATION MAY INCORPORATE TECHNICAL INACCURACIES AND/OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. DRIVERSAFETY USA ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR, AND DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY FOR, ANY SUCH INACCURACIES, ERRORS, OR OMISSIONS.DRIVERSAFETY USA MAY MAKE CHANGES TO THE COURSES AND ANY RELATED DOCUMENTATION, THE WEB SITE AND ANY CONTENT CONTAINED THEREIN OR TO THIS OR ANY OTHER POLICY RELATING THERETO AND MAY DO SO BY UPDATING THE RELEVANT POSTING. YOU ARE BOUND BY ANY SUCH REVISIONS AND SHOULD THEREFORE PERIODICALLY VISIT THIS PAGE TO REVIEW THE THEN CURRENT DISCLAIMERS AND STATEMENTS OF POLICY TO WHICH YOU ARE BOUND.NO RIGHTS TO VOLUNTEERED INFORMATIONShould you respond with information, feedback, data, questions, comments, and/or suggestions, with the exception of information subject to the DRIVERSAFETY USA PRIVACY POLICY as disclosed in the DRIVERSAFETY USA PRIVACY POLICY, that response will not be treated as confidential, and DRIVERSAFETY USA shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute the response to others, without limitation. You agree that DRIVERSAFETY USA is free to use any ideas, concepts, algorithms, or techniques contained in your response for any purpose whatsoever, including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing, and marketing products and/or services incorporating your ideas, concepts, algorithms, and techniques. This volunteered information does not impact, in any way, the security or privacy of your personal information subject to the DRIVERSAFETY USA PRIVACY POLICY.COPYRIGHT © 2020 Kassel Enterprises Group LLC.
All rights reserved.
“SAFETY-USA”, “Safety-Ed” and “Ride Safe. Ride Smart.” as well as all of the graphical versions of “SAFETY-USA”, “Safety-Ed”, “Ride Safe. Ride Smart.” and all of the logos and proprietary terms and phrases, including without limitation No claim is made to the exclusive right to use “Ride Safe” apart from the marks noted above.
Other product or brand names used on this Web Site, the Courses or related documentation may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners.
Home |
Course Info |
Enroll |
About Us |
Help |
Contact Us |
Login/Resume Course |
En Español |
